# Vishnuprasad Yelthimar

Infosys

### Summary

Experience in IT Service Management with implementation of ITSM tools for large organisations to enhance the IT infrastructure operations.

Practice Lead for IT Service Management Process and Tools portfolio in Infosys. Responsible for Pre Sales, Solution Development, Program Management, Client Relationship Management, ServiceNow COE and People Management

## Experience

#### **Principal Consultant at Infosys**

October 2015 - Present (1 year 6 months)

#### Senior Project Manager at Infosys

July 2014 - Present (2 years 9 months)

#### Project Manager at Infosys

July 2008 - Present (8 years 9 months)

ITIL, IT Service Management, Pre-Sales, ServiceNow

#### Senior Developer at Symphony Technology Group

September 2006 - June 2008 (1 year 10 months)

ESSBASE, Hyperion development

#### Software Engineer at Accord Software & Systems

July 2003 - August 2006 (3 years 2 months)

Development

## Languages

**English** 

Hindi

Kannada

Konkani

Tulu

#### Certifications

#### **ITIL Foundation 2011**

#### APMG August 2013

### **Servicenow Certified System Administrator**

ServiceNow – The Enterprise Cloud Company February 2015

## Skills & Expertise

Unix

 $\mathbf{C}$ 

C++

**SQL** 

**Core Java** 

**ITIL** 

**IT Service Management** 

**Pre-sales** 

**Global Delivery** 

**Program Management** 

**Service Delivery** 

Servicenow

IT Infrastructure Management

**Requirements Analysis** 

**Software Development** 

**Oracle** 

**Unix Shell Scripting** 

**SDLC** 

**Shell Scripting** 

### Education

#### **NMAMIT**, Nitte

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering, 1999 - 2003

# Vishnuprasad Yelthimar

Infosys



# 2 person has recommended Vishnuprasad

"Vishnuprasad is an experienced Service Now implementation specialist. I had extensive experience working with him to deliver the Service Now solution integrated with alert monitoring toolsets for our joint client. Vishnuprasad managed his team to deliver the related technology work streams against very tight timelines with the client changing requirements last minute. In this area of expertise I would be happy to work with Vishnuprasad again and recommend him for this line of work."

— Patrick Lobo, was with another company when working with Vishnuprasad at Infosys

"I would highly recommend Vishnu, excellent personal skills and gets the job done."

— Stephen Hugh McNeill, was Vishnuprasad's client

Contact Vishnuprasad on LinkedIn